https://comparettolawfirm.com/privacy-policy

MainPrivacy PolicyFirm Contact
Privacy Policy for Comparetto Law FirmAt Comparetto Law Firm, accessible from https://comparettolawfirm.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Comparetto Law Firm and how we use it.If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Comparetto Law Firm. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.ConsentBy using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.Information we collectThe personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, company name, address, email address, and telephone number.How we use your informationWe use the information we collect in various ways, including to:Provide, operate, and maintain our websteImprove, personalize, and expand our websteUnderstand and analyze how you use our websteDevelop new products, services, features, and functionalityCommunicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the webste, and for marketing and promotional purposesSend you emailsFind and prevent fraudLog FilesComparetto Law Firm follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.Advertising Partners Privacy PoliciesYou may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Comparetto Law Firm.Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Comparetto Law Firm, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.Note that Comparetto Law Firm has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.Third Party Privacy PoliciesComparetto Law Firm’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:Request that a business that collects a consumer’s personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.Request that a business that sells a consumer’s personal data, not sell the consumer’s personal data.If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.GDPR Data Protection RightsWe would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.Children’s InformationAnother part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.Comparetto Law Firm does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records. Comparetto Law Firm Accessibility StatementUpdated: December 2019.GeneralComparetto Law Firm strives to ensure that its services are accessible to people with disabilities. Comparetto Law Firm has invested a significant amount of resources to help ensure that its website is made easier to use and more accessible for people with disabilities, with the strong belief that every person has the right to live with dignity, equality, comfort and independence.Accessibility on comparettolawfirm.comcomparettolawfirm.com makes available the UserWay Website Accessibility Widget that is powered by a dedicated accessibility server. The software allows comparettolawfirm.com to improve its compliance with the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG 2.1).Enabling the Accessibility MenuThe comparettolawfirm.com accessibility menu can be enabled by clicking the accessibility menu icon that appears on the corner of the page. After triggering the accessibility menu, please wait a moment for the accessibility menu to load in its entirety.DisclaimerComparetto Law Firm continues its efforts to constantly improve the accessibility of its site and services in the belief that it is our collective moral obligation to allow seamless, accessible and unhindered use also for those of us with disabilities.In an ongoing effort to continually improve and remediate accessibility issues, we also regularly scan comparettolawfirm.com with UserWay’s Accessibility Scanner to identify and fix every possible accessibility barrier on our site. Despite our efforts to make all pages and content on comparettolawfirm.com fully accessible, some content may not have yet been fully adapted to the strictest accessibility standards. This may be a result of not having found or identified the most appropriate technological solution.Here For YouIf you are experiencing difficulty with any content on comparettolawfirm.com or require assistance with any part of our site, please contact us during normal business hours as detailed below and we will be happy to assist.Contact UsIf you wish to report an accessibility issue, have any questions or need assistance, please contact Comparetto Law Firm Customer Support as follows:Email: ajc@comparettolawfirm.comPhone: 1(727) 851-6625
